<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Long Beach's Best Real Estate Training</title>
    <description>Scott Kato, a top Real Estate Agent in Long Beach, shares his own internal real estate agent training for free. His Real Estate Training, Tips and Advice will help you sell more homes in less time.</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 13:20:42 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 13:20:42 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.7.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>How to Stay Top of Mind and Prospect for New Business</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/jQO49hRL-Po?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;center&gt;&lt;em&gt;Here are my tips for staying top of mind with your database and prospecting for new business despite the stay-at-home ordinances sweeping the nation.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/center&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What can you do to stay top of mind with your database and still prospect for business with the stay-at-home ordinance that is in effect?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My team, including our entire market center, is making 10 “I care” calls per day. One of these calls might sound something like this:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Hi, Mrs. Smith! I just wanted to reach out and let you know that I was thinking about you and to see how you were holding up. I believe that we’re all in this together, so I wanted to see if there was anything that I can do to help you. I believe that we’re going to come out of this stronger and more connected than ever.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=When we recently joined forces with Facebook, we became one of their largest clients overnight.%20http://localhost:4000/how-to-stay-top-of-mind-and-prospect-for-new-business.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“When we recently joined forces with Facebook, we became one of their largest clients overnight.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You may be asking yourself, “How do I prospect for new business?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Our office is running Facebook ads through our new Keller Williams CRM system, KW Command&lt;/strong&gt;. When we recently joined forces with Facebook, we became one of their largest clients overnight. Therefore, we get huge discounts on any ad expenditures that we do with them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For example, one of my top agents listed a home just last week. He ran a new ad through our Command system along with Facebook and he generated 120 leads at  $1.63 per click—that’s unheard of! &lt;strong&gt;Had he done it on his own, he could easily have spent over $6 per lead&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you would like to receive the “I care” script or learn more about using our Command CRM system with Facebook, please feel free to reach out to us. We would be more than happy to have a conversation about the growth of your business.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/strategy-call/&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/img/cta-images/full-strategy-call.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Strategy Call&quot; class=&quot;full-post-cta&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2020 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/how-to-stay-top-of-mind-and-prospect-for-new-business.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/how-to-stay-top-of-mind-and-prospect-for-new-business.html</guid>
        
        <category>Buyer Prospects</category>
        
        <category>Lead Generation</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
