<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:itunesu="http://www.itunesu.com/feed" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Long Beach Real Estate Podcast with Scott Kato</title>
    <link>http://localhost:4000</link>
    <atom10:link xmlns:atom10="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="http://localhost:4000"/>
    <description>If you are looking to buy or sell a home, get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from  - your professional Long Beach Real Estate Agents.</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <managingEditor>Scott Kato</managingEditor>
    <lastBuildDate>2020-06-08 13:56:09 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <media:copyright>Scott Kato</media:copyright>
    <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000/img/podcast.jpg"/>
    <media:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Long Beach, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</media:keywords>
    <media:category scheme="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd">Education</media:category>
    <itunes:owner>
      <itunes:email>scott@coachkato.com</itunes:email>
      <itunes:name>Scott Kato</itunes:name>
    </itunes:owner>
    <itunes:author>Scott Kato</itunes:author>
    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    <itunes:image href="http://localhost:4000/img/podcast.jpg"/>
    <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Long Beach, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
    <itunes:subtitle>Learn all the tips, tricks and more for buyers and sellers in the Long Beach Area Real Estate Market</itunes:subtitle>
    <itunes:summary>If you are looking to buy or sell a home, get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from  - your professional Long Beach Real Estate Agents.</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:category text="Education"/>
    
      <item>
        <title>How Can I Stay Productive While Working From Home?</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/how-can-i-stay-productive-while-working-from-home.html</link>
        
          <category>Transaction Management</category>
        
        <author>Scott Kato</author>
        <pubDate>2020-05-20 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Scott+Kato/Videos/2020/How+Can+I+Stay+Productive+While+Working+From+Home_.mp4</guid>
        <description>

How can you stay productive while working from home?

I’ve been working from home, and I’ll admit that I’m not very disciplined at all, meaning that, absent some kind of routine, I will inevitably end up doing one of two things: working constantly and ignoring the people I love or never actually starting my workday at all. Obviously, my family doesn’t love the first scenario, my business partners don’t love the second, and truthfully, I’m not a fan of either.

Despite my lifelong dream of living outside of any structure, I designed a workday for myself and you should too.

Working remotely means that no one is going to impose a routine for you. There are no set times for breaks or a clearly defined end-of-work time. You have to decide on all this for yourself.

Setting up a routine keeps your work-life balance from tipping too much toward work or life. It’s easy to fall into bad habits at the office, and it’s even easier when you work from home. I recommend not immediately starting your workday when you wake up. Give yourself some time for breakfast, reading, meditation, or texting a friend.

Also, be sure to take breaks—actual breaks—throughout the day. Give your brain some time away from the task at hand; the usual pauses to talk to coworkers don’t happen at home, so you have to create them.

“Routine automates discipline, and being stuck in a routine is preferable to not having one.”

Keeping the balance is critical. It’s not healthy to allow work to take over every minute of your day, and it’s also not particularly productive. Without a routine, your workspace and home will blur together, which is why it’s also important to have a dedicated workspace that your family respects as your workspace. This will help create a mental separation of being at work from being at home.

This also isn’t just about productivity—not setting these boundaries can also make your home life worse, especially with other people in the house. My kids would often come to ask me questions while I’m in a video meeting or on a call, and I’ve said things I regret to get them to go away. Getting angry when your concentration is broken can throw you off longer than it should.

Ideally, your workspace will be one with a door that closes, but that isn’t mandatory. Currently, my office is my outdoor courtyard; I move my essentials to the patio table every morning around 7:45 a.m. until 1:30 p.m. When the sun moves, I move with it, and I’ve found that the change of environment gives me a new perspective that helps me to see things differently.

Routine automates discipline, and being stuck in a routine is preferable to not having one. You need to design systems that work for you and stick to them. Routines make this a lot easier by removing decisions from your day-to-day.

If you have any questions or comments, don’t hesitate to reach out to me. I’d love to hear from you.


  

</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Scott+Kato/Videos/2020/How+Can+I+Stay+Productive+While+Working+From+Home_.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Scott+Kato/Videos/2020/How+Can+I+Stay+Productive+While+Working+From+Home_.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>How can you stay productive while working from home?</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Scott Kato</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>How can you stay productive while working from home?</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Long Beach, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>How to Stay Top of Mind and Prospect for New Business</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/how-to-stay-top-of-mind-and-prospect-for-new-business.html</link>
        
          <category>Buyer Prospects</category>
        
          <category>Lead Generation</category>
        
        <author>Scott Kato</author>
        <pubDate>2020-04-30 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Scott+Kato/Videos/2020/How+to+Stay+Top+of+Mind+and+Prospect+for+New+Business.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Here are my tips for staying top of mind with your database and prospecting for new business despite the stay-at-home ordinances sweeping the nation.

What can you do to stay top of mind with your database and still prospect for business with the stay-at-home ordinance that is in effect?

My team, including our entire market center, is making 10 “I care” calls per day. One of these calls might sound something like this:

“Hi, Mrs. Smith! I just wanted to reach out and let you know that I was thinking about you and to see how you were holding up. I believe that we’re all in this together, so I wanted to see if there was anything that I can do to help you. I believe that we’re going to come out of this stronger and more connected than ever.”

“When we recently joined forces with Facebook, we became one of their largest clients overnight.”

You may be asking yourself, “How do I prospect for new business?”

Our office is running Facebook ads through our new Keller Williams CRM system, KW Command. When we recently joined forces with Facebook, we became one of their largest clients overnight. Therefore, we get huge discounts on any ad expenditures that we do with them.

For example, one of my top agents listed a home just last week. He ran a new ad through our Command system along with Facebook and he generated 120 leads at  $1.63 per click—that’s unheard of! Had he done it on his own, he could easily have spent over $6 per lead.

If you would like to receive the “I care” script or learn more about using our Command CRM system with Facebook, please feel free to reach out to us. We would be more than happy to have a conversation about the growth of your business.


  

</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Scott+Kato/Videos/2020/How+to+Stay+Top+of+Mind+and+Prospect+for+New+Business.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Scott+Kato/Videos/2020/How+to+Stay+Top+of+Mind+and+Prospect+for+New+Business.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Here are my tips for staying top of mind with your database and prospecting for new business despite the stay-at-home ordinances.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Scott Kato</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Here are my tips for staying top of mind with your database and prospecting for new business despite the stay-at-home ordinances.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Long Beach, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
    <copyright>Scott Kato</copyright>
    <media:credit role="author">Scott Kato</media:credit>
    <media:rating>nonadult</media:rating>
    <media:description type="plain">If you are looking to buy or sell a home, get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from  - your professional Long Beach Real Estate Agents.</media:description>
  </channel>
</rss>
